imagine a student goes to Spain for
higher studies or a businessman goes
there for his regular business meeting
and both of them losing the one bag they
can't afford to lose on top of it they
get stuck with some medical emergencies
challenges like these can spoil your
plans HDFC are good travel insurance has
following benefits no pre-policy medical
checkups one lakh cashless Network
hospitals worldwide
24 7 worldwide assistance hassle-free
clean process
coverage for covid-19 hospitalization
HDFC Argo also provides medical related
coverage which includes emergency
medical expenses emergency dental
expenses medical evacuation Hospital
daily cash allowance medical and body
repatriation accidental death
baggage related coverage which includes
loss of baggage and personal documents
loss of checked in package delay of
checked in baggage
Journey related coverage which includes
personal liability Financial emergency
assistance hijack distress allowance
flight delay Hotel accommodation
because we at HDFC Argo we know your
world